Guide to the Secretary of the University of Pittsburgh, John Weber, Administrative Files, 1936-1956 UA.3.4.1A
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Zoology Department (Box 25, Folder 227)
- Subject Index File (Box 25, Folder 229)